<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sahil Deo</title>
    <link>https://sahildeo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sahil Deo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sahildeo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sahildeo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sahildeo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Sahil is a co-founder of CPC Analytics, a data-driven consulting firm with offices in Berlin and Pune. As a part of CPC, he has consulted leading private and public sector organizations such as Siemens, Mitsubishi Materials, the World Health Organization and GIZ (German International Cooperation).
Prior to founding CPC, Sahil worked for GIZ (German International Cooperation) in Tanzania alongside the Prime Minister’s Office, to streamline the revenue collection process in Local Government Agencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media, Podcasts etc.</title>
      <link>https://sahildeo.github.io/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sahildeo.github.io/media/</guid>
      <description>  Algorithmic Accountability in India: Deployment of AI systems by the state and the need for transparency, MediaNama, 10/06/2020
  On the frontline, Hindustan Times, 15/4/2020
  Pune firm, CPC Analytics, is India’s finalist for global innovation contest, Hindustan Times, 20/09/19
  The Coronavirus Pandemic: Data and Technology Implications on Citizen-State Relations, Centre for Policy Research, 07/05/2020 - alongside Ananth Padmanabhan &amp;amp; Yamini Aiyar
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Select Articles</title>
      <link>https://sahildeo.github.io/shortform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sahildeo.github.io/shortform/</guid>
      <description>  Heralding a new health data regime in India | Observer Research Foundation, 06/7/2020 Co-Authored with Subhodeep Jash
  Unacademy, Byju’s help clear your doubts, but have few answers on data privacy | The Print, 21/5/2020 Co-Authored with Subhodeep Jash
  Central Bank Digital Currency in India: Deeper engagement and thorough exploration needed before execution | Observer Research Foundation, 21/5/2020 Co-Authored with Shardul Manurkar
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Select Publications</title>
      <link>https://sahildeo.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sahildeo.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Fast Data for Faster Decision-making: The Utility of High-frequency Economic Indicators ORF Issue Brief No. 372, June 2020, Observer Research Foundation Co-Authored with Sanjana Krishnan and Pooja Verulkar
50 Days of Lockdown: Measuring India’s Success in Arresting COVID-19 ORF Special Report No. 107, May 2020, Observer Research Foundation. Co-Authored with Sanjana Krishnan and Shardul Manurkar
Building India’s Global Health Strategy: Beyond the Role of ‘Pharmacist of the World’ ORF Special Report No.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>